Audrey Beck Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series II: House of Representatives, undated, 1959-1978
  - Subseries H: Meskill Policies, 1969-1975
    - Meskill
      - Health Center, 1972-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 472)
      - Health Department, 1971-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 473)
      - Higher Education, 1973-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 474)
      - Impoundment, 1973-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 475)
      - Legislation, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 476)
      - Program, 1971-1973 (Box 10:, Folder 477)
      - Revenue Sharing, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 478)
      - Speech—Economic Development, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 479)
      - Speeches, 1971-1973 (Box 10:, Folder 480)
      - State personnel, 1971-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 481)
      - Staff salary, 1971-1973 (Box 10:, Folder 482)
      - State Police, 1972-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 483)
      - Tax Reform, 1972-1973 (Box 10:, Folder 484)
      - Utilities, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 485)
      - Welfare, 1969-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 486)
      - Welfare, 1971-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 487)
    - Monorail, 1973-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 488)
    - Public Relations, 1973-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 489)
    - Rocky Hill Veterans Hospital, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 490)
    - Special Assistants, 1973-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 491)
    - State Employees, 1971-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 492)
    - State Employees Bonus, 1973 (Box 10:, Folder 493)
    - Tax cut, 1972-1973 (Box 10:, Folder 494)
    - Utility Tax, 1974 (Box 10:, Folder 495)
    - Vetoes, 1971-1974 (Box 10:, Folder 496)
- Series III: State Senate, undated, 1930-1982
  - Subseries A: Subject Files, undated, 1930-1982
    - Aging, 1974-1980 (Box 11:, Folder 497)
    - Agricultural lands, 1977 (Box 11:, Folder 498)
    - Agricultural lands, 1978 (Box 11:, Folder 499)
    - Agricultural lands, 1979-1981 (Box 11:, Folder 500)
    - Air quality, 1976-1979 (Box 11:, Folder 501)
    - Air quality, 1978-1979 (Box 11:, Folder 502)
    - Alcoholism, 1975-1976 (Box 11:, Folder 503)
    - Animal fees, 1975 (Box 11:, Folder 504)
    - Asbestos, 1977-1978 (Box 11:, Folder 505)
    - Awards, 1968-1976 (Box 11:, Folder 506)
    - Banking, 1975-1976 (Box 11:, Folder 507)
    - Banking, 1977-1978 (Box 11:, Folder 508)
    - Banking and business, 1955-1979 (Box 11:, Folder 509)
    - Beck
      - Bills, 1969-1972 (Box 11:, Folder 510)
      - Clippings, 1977-1979 (Box 11:, Folder 511)
      - Statements, 1978-1979 (Box 11:, Folder 512)
    - Business Coalitions: Capital Area Health Consortium, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 513)
    - Calendar and dates, 1982 (Box 11:, Folder 514)
    - Carcinogens: Union Water Works—Moosup, 1977 (Box 11:, Folder 515)
    - Carcinogens in water, 1974-1977 (Box 11:, Folder 516)
    - Carcinogens in water, 1976-1977 (Box 11:, Folder 517)
    - Carcinogens in water, 1976-1977 (Box 11:, Folder 518)
    - Carcinogens: Water supply, 1977 (Box 11:, Folder 519)
    - Career management, undated (Box 11:, Folder 520)
    - Catholic Church: Reilly, 1975 (Box 11:, Folder 521)
    - Central Connecticut—Adjunct Professor, 1974 (Box 11:, Folder 522)
    - Child protection, 1979-1981 (Box 11:, Folder 523)
    - Cities, 1977-1978 (Box 11:, Folder 524)
    - City and Town Development Act, 1975 (Box 12:, Folder 525)
    - Commuter bus service, 1979 (Box 12:, Folder 526)
    - Collective bargaining and AAUP, 1979 (Box 12:, Folder 527)
    - Connecticut General, 1981 (Box 12:, Folder 528)
    - Connecticut Humanities Council, 1978-1979 (Box 12:, Folder 529)
    - Connecticut Humanities Council, 1979 (Box 12:, Folder 530-532)
    - Connecticut Humanities Council, 1980 (Box 12:, Folder 533)
    - Connecticut Humanities Council, 1981 (Box 12:, Folder 534)
    - Connecticut Regional Medical Program, 1971-1972 (Box 12:, Folder 535)
    - Constituents' requests, 1975-1979 (Box 12:, Folder 536)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 12:, Folder 537)
    - Council of State Governments, 1981 (Box 12:, Folder 538)
    - Council on Human Services, 1975-1976 (Box 12:, Folder 539)
    - Crime and police, 1979-1983 (Box 12:, Folder 540)
    - Delegate letter, 1978 (Box 12:, Folder 541)
    - Elderly Department, 1976 (Box 12:, Folder 542)
    - Environment, 1975-1980 (Box 12:, Folder 543)
    - Environmental Recreation Plan, 1978 (Box 12:, Folder 544)
    - Environmental Review Teams, 1976-1977 (Box 12:, Folder 545)
    - Ethics Code, 1979 (Box 12:, Folder 546)
    - Expense sheet, undated (Box 12:, Folder 547)
    - Farmland Values, 1976-1977 (Box 12:, Folder 548)
    - Farmland Values, 1978 (Box 12:, Folder 549)
    - Food Supplies, 1975-1976 (Box 13:, Folder 550)
    - General Assembly notebook, 1974-1978 (Box 13:, Folder 551-552)
    - General Assembly Reports and Directory, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 553)
    - GOP, 1975 (Box 13:, Folder 554)
    - Governor's proposals: Special legislative session, 1981 (Box 13:, Folder 555)
    - Gun control, 1975 (Box 13:, Folder 556)
    - HABITAT, 1976 (Box 13:, Folder 557-558)
    - Hazardous waste: UConn, 1980-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 559)
    - Hazardous waste: UConn, 1979-1983 (Box 13:, Folder 560)
    - Health Department: State, 1975 (Box 13:, Folder 561)
    - Hepatitis—Mansfield Training School, 1976 (Box 13:, Folder 562)
    - Home District, 1975 (Box 13:, Folder 563)
    - Home District, 1976 (Box 13:, Folder 564)
    - Houley, Robert: State Senator, 1975-1976 (Box 13:, Folder 565)
    - Housing: State, 1979 (Box 13:, Folder 566)
    - Housing and Urban Development(HUD) National Conference, 1979 (Box 13:, Folder 567-569)
    - Hughes, Doris: Minorities, 1974-1975 (Box 13:, Folder 570)
    - I-84 Yes Committee, 1975-1982 (Box 13:, Folder 571)
    - Invitations and letters, 1979-1980 (Box 13:, Folder 572)
    - Joint Committee on Legislation Management, 1981-1982 (Box 13:, Folder 573)
    - Legislation, 1975 (Box 13:, Folder 574)
    - Legislative Accomplishments, 1975 (Box 13:, Folder 575)
    - Legislative Program Review and Investigations Committee (LPR & IC), 1980 (Box 13:, Folder 576)
    - Letters: Endorsements, 1977-1978 (Box 13:, Folder 577)
    - Letters: Pending Bills, 1978-1980 (Box 13:, Folder 578)
    - Lobbyists, registered, 1975-1976 (Box 13:, Folder 579)
    - Mansfield Training School (MTS), 1975 (Box 13:, Folder 580)
    - Maps: Voting districts, undated (Box 13:, Folder 581)
    - Mental Health, 1972-1975 (Box 13:, Folder 582)
    - Mental Health, 1974-1979 (Box 13:, Folder 583)
    - Mental Health, 1977-1981 (Box 13:, Folder 584)
    - Mental Health, 1982 (Box 13:, Folder 585)
    - Mental Health budget, 1975-1976 (Box 14:, Folder 586)
    - Mental Health Services Act, 1974 (Box 14:, Folder 587)
    - Mental Health System, 1979-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 588)
    - Mental Health Talk, 1980-1982 (Box 14:, Folder 589)
    - Mental Hospital Closure report, 1981 (Box 14:, Folder 590)
    - National Agricultural Land System Source Books, 1981 (Box 14:, Folder 591)
    - National Federation of State Humanities Councils Booklet, 1982 (Box 14:, Folder 592)
    - Norwich Adolescent Unit, 1974-1975 (Box 14:, Folder 593)
    - Norwich Hospital, 1977-1979 (Box 14:, Folder 594)
    - Nuclear weapons, 1982 (Box 14:, Folder 595)
    - Nurses—letters, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 596)
    - Nursing, 1973-1975 (Box 14:, Folder 598)
    - Nursing Homes, 1975-1979 (Box 14:, Folder 599)
    - Open Vote, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 600)
    - OSHA—Federalized, 1977 (Box 14:, Folder 601)
    - Power: Nuclear, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 602)
    - Private sector contributions, 1980 (Box 14:, Folder 603)
    - Property tax and tax exempt land report, 1930 (Box 14:, Folder 604)
    - Providence and Worchester Company Railroad, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 605)
    - Proxmire, William: Senator, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 606)
    - Public Health and Safety, 1974-1975 (Box 14:, Folder 607)
    - Public Health and Safety, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 608)
    - Public Health and Safety, 1976-1977 (Box 14:, Folder 609)
    - Public Works Projects, 1976 (Box 14:, Folder 610)
    - Railroads, 1975-1977 (Box 14:, Folder 611)
    - Reforms, 1974-1975 (Box 14:, Folder 612)
    - Revitalization Corporations, 1979 (Box 14:, Folder 613)
    - Sexual crimes, 1979-1981 (Box 14:, Folder 614)
    - South Africa n Investments, 1981 (Box 14:, Folder 615)
    - South Windsor, 1978 (Box 14:, Folder 616)
    - Special Session, 1975 (Box 14:, Folder 617)
    - Staff, 1975-1977 (Box 15:, Folder 618)
    - State Central Committee, 1971-1978 (Box 15:, Folder 619)
    - State Employee Study, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 620)
    - State Employees, 1975-1977 (Box 15:, Folder 621-623)
    - State Employees' Personnel Department, 1974-1978 (Box 15:, Folder 624)
    - State Ethics Commission, 1979-1980 (Box 15:, Folder 625)
    - State Police—Doris Hughes, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 626)
    - Stearns, Luther Beck opponent, 1976 (Box 15:, Folder 627)
    - Stowe-Day House, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 628)
    - Supreme Court Brief, 1981 (Box 15:, Folder 629)
    - Taylor, Phil, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 630)
    - Unemployment Compensation, 1975-1977 (Box 15:, Folder 631-632)
    - Union Station, 1977-1981 (Box 15:, Folder 633)
    - United Nations Conference, 1976 (Box 15:, Folder 634-636)
    - University Planning, 1975 (Box 15:, Folder 637-638)
    - Upward Mobility—Job reclassification, 1978-1979 (Box 16:, Folder 639-640)
    - Veto session, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 641)
    - Veto session, 1976 (Box 16:, Folder 642)
    - Welfare, 1975-1976 (Box 16:, Folder 643)
    - Welfare, 1978-1979 (Box 16:, Folder 644)
    - Welfare Department, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 645)
    - Writings on politics: Sattor, Lerner, 1981 (Box 16:, Folder 646)
    - Youth and Public Works, 1977-1979 (Box 16:, Folder 647)
  - Subseries B: American Society of Planning Officials, 1971-1977
    - ASPO, 1971-1973 (Box 16:, Folder 648)
    - ASPO, 1971-1974 (Box 16:, Folder 649)
    - ASPO, 1971-1977 (Box 16:, Folder 650)
    - ASPO, 1972-1973 (Box 16:, Folder 651)
    - ASPO, 1973 (Box 16:, Folder 652)
    - ASPO, 1973-1974 (Box 16:, Folder 653)
    - ASPO, 1974-1977 (Box 16:, Folder 654)
    - ASPO, 1975-1976 (Box 16:, Folder 655)
    - ASPO, 1976 (Box 16:, Folder 656)
    - ASPO, 1976-1977 (Box 16:, Folder 657)
    - ASPO Minutes, 1972-1973 (Box 16:, Folder 658)
    - First Church of Christ—Historic District Funding, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 659)
    - National Planning Conference, 1977 (Box 16:, Folder 660-662)
    - State and Urban Development, 1975 (Box 16:, Folder 663)
  - Subseries C: Beck Organizations, 1974-1979
    - American Institute of Planners (AIP), 1977-1978 (Box 16:, Folder 664)
    - Area Cooperative Special Education, 1978 (Box 16:, Folder 665)
    - Arts Foundation, 1978 (Box 16:, Folder 666)
    - Binding Arbitration, 1978 (Box 16:, Folder 667)
    - Committee to Study the Solicitation of CT Rides in Motor Vehicles, 1974 (Box 16:, Folder 668)
    - Connecticut Association of Boards of Education (CABE), 1977 (Box 16:, Folder 669)
    - Council of State Governments, 1975-1977 (Box 16:, Folder 670)
    - Eastern CT State College, 1975-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 671)
    - Emergency Medical Services, 1974-1978 (Box 17:, Folder 672)
    - Fireman's Association, 1974-1976 (Box 17:, Folder 673)
    - First Women's Bank, 1976-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 674)
    - Food Emergency Action Development (FEAD), 1977-1978 (Box 17:, Folder 675)
    - Girl Scouts, 1976-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 676)
    - Grange, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 677)
    - Habitat, 1977 (Box 17:, Folder 678)
    - Hartford Chamber of Commerce, 1976 (Box 17:, Folder 679)
    - Hartford Regional Market, 1976-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 680)
    - I-84, 1975-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 681)
    - Intern Program, 1976-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 682)
    - Legal Assistance, 1974-1979 (Box 17:, Folder 683)
    - Litter Control Act, 1977 (Box 17:, Folder 684)
    - Mansfield Day Treatment Center, 1977 (Box 17:, Folder 685)
    - Mansfield Training School, 1975-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 686)
    - National Conference of State Legislators, 1975-1978 (Box 17:, Folder 687)
    - Science and Technology, 1977-1979 (Box 17:, Folder 688)
    - Newington Children's Hospital, 1975-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 689)
    - Northeastern Area Regional Education Services, 1977 (Box 17:, Folder 690)
    - Northeastern CT Community Development Corporation, 1974-1976 (Box 17:, Folder 691)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1977 (Box 17:, Folder 692)
    - Recommendations, 1977-1978 (Box 17:, Folder 693)
    - State Depository, 1977 (Box 17:, Folder 694)
    - State Elections Commission, 1976-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 695)
    - Stevens (J.P.) Boycott, 1976-1978 (Box 17:, Folder 696)
    - United Nations Conference, 1976 (Box 17:, Folder 697)
    - Vacation Travel Council, 1977 (Box 17:, Folder 698)
    - Vita, 1975-1977 (Box 17:, Folder 699)
    - White House Conference on Balanced Nutritional Growth, 1978 (Box 17:, Folder 700)
  - Subseries D: Bills, undated, 1969-1983
    - Aid to Towns, 1974-1975 (Box 17:, Folder 701)
    - Amendments, undated (Box 17:, Folder 702)
    - Anatomical Donations bill, 1977 (Box 17:, Folder 703)
    - Bills, 1971, 1974 (Box 17:, Folder 704)
    - Bills, 1973 (Box 17:, Folder 705)
    - Bills, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 706)
    - Bills, 1975 (Box 17:, Folder 707)
    - Bills, 1975 (Box 18:, Folder 708-710)
    - Bills, 1976 (Box 18:, Folder 711)
    - Bills, 1977 (Box 18:, Folder 712)
    - Bills, 1980 (Box 18:, Folder 713)
    - Bills, Proposed, 1977 (Box 18:, Folder 714-715)
    - Connecticut Health Facilities, undated (Box 18:, Folder 716)
    - Connecticut Hospitals, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 717)
    - Economic Projections Hearing, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 718)
    - Elderly Housing, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 719)
    - Emergency Employment Bill, 1975 (Box 18:, Folder 720)
    - Emergency Layoffs and Plant relocations, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 721)
    - Energy—Solar, 1978-1979 (Box 18:, Folder 722)
    - Environmental Protection, Department of, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 723)
    - Ethics, 1977 (Box 18:, Folder 724)
    - Ethics, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 725)
    - Female/Minority job information, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 726)
    - Final Copies, 1975 (Box 18:, Folder 727)
    - Finance letters, 1978-1979 (Box 18:, Folder 728)
    - Fiscal Analysis, Office of, 1978-1979 (Box 18:, Folder 729-730)
    - Fiscal impact statements, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 731)
    - Fiscal Management Wilde Committee>, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 732)
    - Flood Control, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 733)
    - Fuel Taxes, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 734)
    - Gasoline dealers, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 735)
    - Grants Study—DFA, 1978 (Box 18:, Folder 736)
    - Grants 29th, 1978-1979 (Box 18:, Folder 737)
    - Hazardous waste, 1981 (Box 18:, Folder 738)
    - Health, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 739)
    - Highway Legislation, 1969, 1977 (Box 18:, Folder 740)
    - Historic preservation, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 741)
    - Home energy, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 742)
    - Home improvement, undated (Box 18:, Folder 743)
    - Household abuse, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 744)
    - Housing: moderate rental bonds, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 745)
    - Human services, 1979 (Box 18:, Folder 746)
    - Humane Society, undated (Box 18:, Folder 747)
    - Information studies, 1975-1978 (Box 18:, Folder 748)
    - Jai Alai, 1977 (Box 19:, Folder 749)
    - Jai Alai, 1978 (Box 19:, Folder 750)
    - Letters: Legislature, 1981-1982 (Box 19:, Folder 751)
    - Medicare, undated (Box 19:, Folder 752)
    - Mental retardation, 1979 (Box 19:, Folder 753)
    - Mohawk Mountain State Park, 1978 (Box 19:, Folder 754)
    - Neglected areas, 1975 (Box 19:, Folder 755)
    - Nuclear waste disposal, 1978 (Box 19:, Folder 756)
    - Petitions, 1982-1983 (Box 19:, Folder 757)
    - Petitions for Quinebaug Valley Community College, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 758)
    - Program evaluation, 1979 (Box 19:, Folder 759)
    - Projections, evaluations, 1975-1976 (Box 19:, Folder 760)
    - Property tax relief Study Committee, undated (Box 19:, Folder 761)
    - Public housing, 1979 (Box 19:, Folder 762)
    - Resolutions, 1976 (Box 19:, Folder 763)
    - Revenue sharing handouts, 1972-1975 (Box 19:, Folder 764)
    - School aid lottery, 1975-1976 (Box 19:, Folder 765)
    - Senate roll call, undated (Box 19:, Folder 766)
    - Vermont address, 1983 (Box 19:, Folder 767)
  - Subseries E: Bottle Bill, 1975-1978
    - Bottle Bill, 1975-1976 (Box 19:, Folder 768)
    - Bottle Bill, 1975-1977 (Box 19:, Folder 769)
    - Bottle Bill, 1975-1978 (Box 19:, Folder 770-771)
    - Bottle Bill, 1976-1977 (Box 19:, Folder 772)
    - Bottle Bill, 1977-1978 (Box 19:, Folder 773)
    - Bottle Bill opposition, 1975-1977 (Box 19:, Folder 774)
    - Glass containers, 1975-1976 (Box 19:, Folder 775)
    - Glass containers, 1975 (Box 19:, Folder 776)
  - Subseries F: Government Organization, undated, 1955-1977
    - File #898 Executive Reorganization, 1977 (Box 20:, Folder 777)
    - Filer Report: Government Restructuring Plans, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 778)
    - Government Administration and Policy committee (GAP), 1975-1976 (Box 20:, Folder 779)
    - Government Administration and Policy committee (GAP), 1977 (Box 20:, Folder 780-781)
    - Government Organization, 1976-1977 (Box 20:, Folder 782)
    - Government Redistricting (29th and 35th) (Box 20:, Folder 783)
    - Government Reorganization, 1955 (Box 20:, Folder 784)
    - Government Reorganization, 1975-1976 (Box 20:, Folder 785)
    - Government Reorganization, 1977 (Box 20:, Folder 786-787)
    - Personnel Reorganization, 1975-1976 (Box 20:, Folder 788)
    - Reorganization, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 789)
    - Reorganization—Permanent process, 1977 (Box 20:, Folder 790)
    - Reorganization of State Government and opposition SB357, undated (Box 20:, Folder 791)
    - Structure of Government, 1968 (Box 20:, Folder 792)
  - Subseries G: Historic Preservation, 1968-1985
    - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission of CT, 1976 (Box 20:, Folder 793)
    - Benedict-Miller House, 1981 (Box 20:, Folder 794)
    - Commerce, Department of, 1978-1980 (Box 20:, Folder 795)
    - Connecticut Historical Commission, 1970 (Box 20:, Folder 796)
    - Connecticut Historical Commission, 1982 (Box 20:, Folder 797)
    - Connecticut History, 1969-1975 (Box 21:, Folder 798)
    - Connecticut History Commons, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 799)
    - Connecticut Preservation Action, 1981 (Box 21:, Folder 800)
    - Connecticut Trust for Historical Preservation, 1978-1982 (Box 21:, Folder 801)
    - Conservation and Development Policies Plan, 1982-1985 (Box 21:, Folder 802)
    - Eastern CT Rural and Industrial Areas Preservation Com., 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 803)
    - Environmental Protection, Department of, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 804)
    - Hartford Architecture Conservancy, 1978-1979 (Box 21:, Folder 805)
    - Hartford Architecture Conservancy, 1981 (Box 21:, Folder 806)
    - Hartford Architecture Conservancy, 1982 (Box 21:, Folder 807)
    - Historic Preservation, 1977-1978 (Box 21:, Folder 808)
    - Historic Preservation, 1978 (Box 21:, Folder 808)
    - Historic Preservation, 1982 (Box 21:, Folder 810)
    - Historical societies, 1971-1977 (Box 21:, Folder 811)
    - History, 1877-1978 (Box 21:, Folder 812)
    - ILL., KY, 1982 (Box 21:, Folder 813)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 1978 (Box 21:, Folder 814)
    - National Trust, 1982 (Box 21:, Folder 815)
    - Northeastern CT Regional Planning Agency, 1974 (Box 21:, Folder 816)
    - Planning and Development Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 21:, Folder 817)
    - Policy and Management, Office of, 1982-1983 (Box 21:, Folder 818)
    - Prudence Crandall House, 1969-1975 (Box 21:, Folder 819)
    - Prudence Crandall House, 1976-1982 (Box 21:, Folder 820)
    - Restoration projects, 1969-1979 (Box 21:, Folder 821)
    - Senator Beck—CT Historic Assets, 1977-1979 (Box 21:, Folder 822)
    - Senator Beck—CT Trust for Historic Preservation, 1978-1979 (Box 21:, Folder 823)
    - Southeastern CT Regional Planning Agency, 1968, 1977 (Box 21:, Folder 824)
    - Windham Regional Planning Agency, 1976 (Box 21:, Folder 825)
  - Subseries H: Issues, 1966-1982
    - Attitudes of CT People, 1966 (Box 22:, Folder 826)
    - Blue Laws, 1975-1977 (Box 22:, Folder 827)
    - Capital Housing Corporations, 1981-1982 (Box 22:, Folder 828)
    - Collective Bargaining, 1974-1979 (Box 22:, Folder 829)
    - Common cause, 1975 (Box 22:, Folder 830)
    - Economy: CT Dep. of Commerce, 1972-1980 (Box 22:, Folder 831)
    - Education, 1975-1978 (Box 22:, Folder 832)
    - Electric Boat, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 833)
    - Ethics, 1977-1978 (Box 22:, Folder 834)
    - Farm Labor Relations, 1975 (Box 22:, Folder 835)
    - Freedom of Information, 1975-1978 (Box 22:, Folder 836)
    - Full Time Officials, 1976 (Box 22:, Folder 837)
    - Guaranteed Tax Base, 1976-1978 (Box 22:, Folder 838)
    - Handicapped, 1976-1978 (Box 22:, Folder 839)
    - Health, 1975-1977 (Box 22:, Folder 840)
    - Health, 1977-1978 (Box 22:, Folder 841)
    - Marijuana letter, 1975 (Box 22:, Folder 842)
    - Refinery, 1974-1975 (Box 22:, Folder 843)
    - School lunches, 1975 (Box 22:, Folder 844)
    - Tax reforms, 1982 (Box 22:, Folder 845)
    - Textbook/busing letter, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 846)
    - UConn, 1972-1982 (Box 22:, Folder 847)
- Series IV: Finance Committee and Fiscal Policy, 1965-1984
  - Subseries A: Subject Files, 1965-1984
    - Administration: Committee on Special Revenue, 1977 (Box 22:, Folder 848)
    - Alcohol licenses, 1977-1978 (Box 22:, Folder 849)
    - Alternative taxes, 1975-1976 (Box 23:, Folder 850)
    - Appropriations (Chair), 1978 (Box 23:, Folder 851)
    - Bipartisan Committee on State Tax Revenue, 1981-1983 (Box 23:, Folder 852)
    - Bipartisan Committee on State Tax Revenue, 1982 (Box 23:, Folder 853)
    - Bipartisan Committee on State Tax Revenue, 1983 (Box 23:, Folder 854)
    - Block Grants, 1982-1983 (Box 23:, Folder 855)
    - Blue Ribbon Commission, 1981-1982 (Box 23:, Folder 856)
    - Board Maps, 1966, 1969 (Box 23:, Folder 857)
    - Bonding, 1975-1978 (Box 23:, Folder 858)
    - Bonding Subcommittee, 1972 (Box 23:, Folder 859)
    - Bradley Airport, 1982 (Box 23:, Folder 860)
    - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 23:, Folder 861)
    - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 23:, Folder 862)
    - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 23:, Folder 863)
    - Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 23:, Folder 864)
    - Budget, 1979-1980 (Box 23:, Folder 865)
    - Budget: Culture and the Arts, 1982 (Box 23:, Folder 866)
    - Budget Estimates, 1977-1978 (Box 23:, Folder 867)
    - Budget: Revenue, 1978-1979 (Box 23:, Folder 868)
    - Budgets, 1980-1984 (Box 23:, Folder 869)
    - Caucus Report, 1975-1979 (Box 24:, Folder 870)
    - Chase Econometrics, 1978-1979 (Box 24:, Folder 871)
    - Clairol Tax Fight, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 872)
    - Committee Against Inflation and Unemployment, 1976 (Box 24:, Folder 873)
    - Committee correspondence, 1975-1977 (Box 24:, Folder 874)
    - Comptroller, Tax dept. figures, reports, 1978-1981 (Box 24:, Folder 875)
    - Connecticut Business Climate, 1976-1977 (Box 24:, Folder 876)
    - Credit Ratings, 1975-1976 (Box 24:, Folder 877)
    - Current economic data, 1978-1980 (Box 24:, Folder 878)
    - Dividends—Committee on Finance, 1975 (Box 24:, Folder 879)
    - Dividends tax, 1975-1977 (Box 24:, Folder 880)
    - Dividends tax, 1976-1978 (Box 24:, Folder 881)
    - Dividends tax proposal, 1975-1977 (Box 24:, Folder 882)
    - Economic development, 1978-1981 (Box 24:, Folder 883)
    - Economy, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 884)
    - Environment Licenses, 1976-1977 (Box 24:, Folder 885)
    - Federal Program Analysis, 1981-1982 (Box 24:, Folder 886)
    - Federal Reserve Report, 1977 (Box 24:, Folder 887)
    - Finance—Bonding, 1975 (Box 24:, Folder 888)
    - Finance Committee, 1975-1977 (Box 24:, Folder 889)
    - Finance Committee development, 1975-1976 (Box 24:, Folder 890)
    - Finance Committee Joint Favorable Reports, 1978 (Box 24:, Folder 891)
    - Finance Committee minutes, 1972-1976 (Box 24:, Folder 892)